{
    "subject": "resource/Anything_Can_Happen",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Jos\u00e9_Ferrer",
    "human_readable": "Anything Can Happen stars Jos\u00e9 Ferrer.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.647831380367279,
            "question": "Can you tell me about any other movies starring Jos\u00e9 Ferrer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.609078586101532,
            "question": "Name a film starring Jos\u00e9 Ferrer."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5636985898017883,
            "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Anything Can Happen'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5056254267692566,
            "question": "Is Jos\u00e9 Ferrer an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39708635210990906,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie that features Jos\u00e9 Ferrer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3670617640018463,
            "question": "What is Jos\u00e9 Ferrer best known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3639995753765106,
            "question": "Are there any awards associated with the film 'Anything Can Happen'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3384229242801666,
            "question": "Who directed the movie 'Anything Can Happen'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.286761611700058,
            "question": "What genre is the movie 'Anything Can Happen' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.274325430393219,
            "question": "When was the movie 'Anything Can Happen' released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Anything Can Happen stars Jos\u00e9 Ferrer.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3322_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the movie 'Anything Can Happen' likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3322_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who directed the movie 'Anything Can Happen'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3322_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any awards associated with the film 'Anything Can Happen'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3322_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3322_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3322_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3322_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3322_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3322_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3322_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3322_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3322_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3322_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3322_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents contain multiple references to Jos\u00e9 Ferrer starring in the movie \"Anything Can Happen\", so this triple is supported by the information provided."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Jos\u00e9 Ferrer is one of the starring actors in \"Anything Can Happen,\" along with Kim Hunter."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}